tfportal.de 2011-05-10

# Impressum « Article « All about Team Fortress - TF2 - TFC - FF

## **Webmaster**

Sven 'MeeB' Scholz  
Elsa-Brändström-Weg 36  
48165 Münster

E-Mail senden!

**Inhaltlich Verantwortlicher gemäß § 6 MDStV:**

Sven 'MeeB' Scholz  
Elsa-Brändström-Weg 36  
48165 Münster

## Privacy & Policy

TFPortal.de respects the privacy of its online visitors and community members. We recognize the importance of protecting information collected from users and have adopted this privacy policy that guides how we gather, store, and use information from the use of of our online site.

Please note that this policy may be amended from time to time to reflect changes and additions to the privacy policy. Please check back for the most current version before relying on any of the provisions in this privacy policy. **  
**

**Collection and Use of Information  
** By using TFPortal.de, users agree that TFPortal.de may collect aggregate information, individual information, and personally identifiable information, as defined below. TFPortal.de may share aggregate information and individual information with other parties. TFPortal.de shall not share personally identifiable information with other parties, except as described in the policy below.

"Aggregate information" is information that describes the habits, usage patterns, and demographics of users as a group but does not describe or reveal the identity of any particular user.

"Individual information" is information about a user that is presented in a form distinguishable from information relating to other users but not in a form that personally identifies any user or enables the recipient to communicate directly with any user unless agreed to by the user in advance of such communication.

TFPortal.de may release personally identifiable information to comply with court orders or laws that require us to disclose such information

**Corrections, Updates and Removal of Information  
** If you are concerned about the accuracy of personal information maintained by TFPortal.de or would like your personal information removed from TFPortal.de's records, please contact us by emailing sven@tfportal.de for review, update, or removal of personal information.
